ABIGAIL SCRIPT (demo)

This is the demo version of Abigail Script with default lowercase and uppercase characters and numbers. Free for personal use only. For commercial use and/or full version please visit:

store.rolandhuse.com 

or email me:

contact@rolandhuse.com

Full version contains punctuation, stylistic alternates, standard ligatures, swashes and more. 

You MAY NOT sell my fonts or claim them as your own.
You MAY NOT edit or rename my fonts.

You MAY redistribute my fonts if:
1. You credit me (Roland Huse).
2. Keep the READ ME file intact within the zip folder.
3. Provide a link back to my website (www.rolandhuse.com).

Thank you & I hope you like this font,

Roland

Follow my work on instagram @rolandhusedesign

Poster artwork background image is with the beautiful model Cecilia by the awesome photographer Yvonne Lukas @lensflower